(Raj:)I had no idea
(Raj:)tortilla chips were
such a good fuel source.
(Leonard:)They're basically pure
hydrocarbons soaked in fat.
(Leonard:)Let's hope the lug nut expands.
(Sheldon:)What if that burning
food attracts animals?
(Howard:)We have plenty of food
for the animals.
(Bernadette:)We do?
WOLOWITZ: Yep.
(Howard:)A six-foot wiener
in a Flash T-shirt.
(Sheldon:)That's not very nice.
(Leonard:)It's a bachelor party.
Lighten up.
(electric crackling)
(Sheldon:)What is that awful smell?
(Howard:)It's burning salsa.
(Howard:)I'm hoping the acidity
and salinity
(Howard:)combined with electricity
will corrode the lug nut off.
(Sheldon:)What an innovative solution.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps I don't give your
MIT education enough credit.
Yeah, I saw it on Mythbusters.
(metal scraping metal)
(Sheldon:)All right, this rust,
combined with the aluminum
recovered from the van,
(Sheldon:)is now thermite.
(Leonard:)Great.
Couple pinches
ought to do the trick.